(upbeat disco music)
♪ Ooh, ooh ♪
♪ You can dance, you can jive ♪
♪ Having the time of your life ♪
♪ Ooh, see that girl, watch that scene ♪
♪ Diggin' the dancing queen ♪
♪ Friday night and the lights are low ♪
♪ Looking out for a place to go ♪
♪ Where they play the right music ♪
♪ Getting in the swing ♪
♪ You come to look for a king ♪
♪ Anybody could be that guy ♪
♪ Night is young and the music's high ♪
♪ With a bit of rock music ♪
♪ Everything is fine ♪
♪ You're in the mood for a dance ♪
♪ And when you get the chance ♪
♪ You are the dancing queen ♪
♪ Young and sweet, only 17 ♪
♪ Dancing queen ♪
♪ Feel the beat from the
tambourine, oh yeah ♪
♪ You can dance, you can jive ♪
♪ Having the time of your life ♪
♪ Ooh, see that girl, watch that scene ♪
♪ Diggin' the dancing queen ♪
♪ You're a teaser, you turn 'em on ♪
♪ Leave 'em burning and then you're gone ♪
♪ Looking out for
another, anyone will do ♪
♪ You're in the mood for a dance ♪
♪ And when you get the chance ♪
♪ You are the dancing queen ♪
♪ Young and sweet, only 17 ♪
♪ Dancing queen ♪
♪ Feel the beat from the
tambourine, oh yeah ♪
♪ You can dance, you can jive ♪
♪ Having the time of your life ♪
♪ Oh, see that girl, watch that scene ♪
♪ Diggin' the dancing queen ♪